slipstick.com 2002-12-10

# Privacy Policy for Slipstick Systems Outlook and Exchange Solutions Center

Our privacy policy at the Slipstick Systems Outlook & Exchange Solutions Center is based on two simple principles:

  * Visitors deserve maximum access to information without the need to provide any kind of personal identification. This is why we do not ask you to log on and why our feedback and other forms that collect information don't require you to give your name.

  * As a professionally run site, we need to track certain _aggregate_ information about site visitors to report to the sponsors who financially support the site and to help us understand how you, our visitors, are using the site. 

### Information We Collect Directly from You

On the Slipstick Systems Outlook and Exchange Solutions Center Feedback page and other pages that ask you to fill out a form, you may give as much or as little information as you choose. The more information you provide, the better we can serve you. For example, we cannot respond directly to your feedback form comments unless you provide an email address.

Any such personally identifying information is kept in strictest confidence by Turtleflock, LLC, the parent company of Slipstick Systems Outlook & Exchange Solutions Center. We do not provide it to any other party without asking you first and will use it only for the specific purpose explained on the page where you submit your information. 

### Exchange Messaging Outlook Mailing List

The mailing list for our Exchange Messaging Outlook newsletter is maintained at [Yahoo! Groups](http://groups.yahoo.com/group/emo-newsletter). However, you do not have to join Yahoo! to [ subscribe](mailto:emo-newsletter-subscribe@yahoogroups.com?subject=Subscribe%20to%20EMO), and we will do rent that mailing list to third parties. 

### Information Collected by Third Parties on Our Behalf

We use two independent companies to monitor pages at the Slipstick Systems Outlook & Exchange Solutions Center for general web traffic and statistics related to advertising on the site. While both companies use image tags (so-called "web bugs") to collect information on site visitors, individual visitors remain anonymous. The firms collect and report to us data only in the aggregate, never connecting it with any individual site visitor. 

General web traffic monitoring is handled by the Hitbox Enterprise service, which provides a more accurate picture of how visitors arrive at the site and what they do while they're here than we could obtain from basic log analysis. When permitted by the user, HitBox will place a cookie on your system to help track information about how often you return to the site. The HitBox [ privacy policy](http://www.websidestory.com/cgi-bin/wss.cgi?privacy&privacy&index) reads in part: 

> We do not receive any personal information submitted to third party sites using our HitBox service. Our HitBox service does not collect or report any such information and we do not allow our HitBox clients to deliver this information to us. Because we receive no such personal information from visitors to our HitBox clients' sites, we cannot associate, merge or link any anonymous information we do receive with any personal information of any Internet users.

Banner ads and clicks on certain links are monitored for our sponsors by the AdRunner service, which also collects no personal information.

### Affiliate Programs

In addition, we participate in several affiliate programs that track clicks on specific links so that any purchases you make at affiliated sites may be credited to us, thus producing a modest (very modest) revenue stream that helps us maintain the site. We do not have any control over the privacy policy at those sites or at any of the hundreds of other third-party sites that you can reach through the links on our pages. However, as far as we know, they collect no personal data other than information you provide when you make a purchase.
